{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbd6ff124495ad843fae"},"product_asin":"B09DGBS1HV","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date??","answer":"Hi, glad to know of your interest. Colgate Total Whole Mouth Health toothpaste is best to use before 24 months from the manufacturing date. While we won‚Äôt be able to share specific information for the product that would be shipped to you, this information is printed on the packaging as well as on the rear/crimp end of the toothpaste tube in \"MM/YY\" format ( MM represents the month and YY the year of manufacture). Hope we have answered your question. Thanks!\"see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbd6ff124495ad843fb0"},"product_asin":"B00U2DT3H6","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have fluoride","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"VASUDEV COMMODITY","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbd7ff124495ad843fb2"},"product_asin":"B09QRTXCWD","QAs":[{"question":"Can 6 year old kid can use","answer":"Hell No!! Generally kids swallow the toothpaste!! It's filled with such chemicals which r nt safe for children","votes":"0","username":"sunil dash","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it vegetarian ?","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"sunil dash","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain fluoride?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"AMIT_X_LUCIFER","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we used for this daily regular brush?","answer":"Yes, Visible White O2 toothpaste with active oxygen whitening technology is enamel-safe. It is also a daily anticavity fluoride toothpaste that provides not only whitening but also daily oral care. Thanks for writing in Raghavendra!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the ingredients as it is not in description please tell me i am buying it this question is for seller only","answer":"Mat khareedna bhai, itna drastic or major whiteness nahi ajayega... trust me on this.. I have used this for 3mnth twice in a day.. kuch itna farak nahi aya h abhi tak","votes":"0","username":"sunil dash","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this product ?","answer":"It may differ frm batch to batch.","votes":"0","username":"sunil dash","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is O2 a vegan toothpaste?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"sunil dash","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbd9ff124495ad843fbc"},"product_asin":"B09QRL1M8Y","QAs":[{"question":"25 gm or 250 gm??","answer":"Hi, glad to know your interest. It is a 25g Colgate Visible White O2, Peppermint Sparkle toothpaste. Hope this helps to clarify. Thanks for getting in touch with us!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-07-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdbff124495ad843fc0"},"product_asin":"B09QSBPKTF","QAs":[{"question":"How much Past should use on brush?","answer":"Pea Size only","votes":"0","username":"aswedlock","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the taste of the toothpaste?","answer":"No taste","votes":"0","username":"aswedlock","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdbff124495ad843fc5"},"product_asin":"B09QRQQL51","QAs":[{"question":"Is it chemically corrosive to teeth?","answer":"It's safe to use. Don't worry","votes":"0","username":"dan","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about Tobacco spot","answer":"Hi Alisha, Colgate Visible White O2 toothpaste, is formulated with a unique active oxygen technology with a clinically proven claim of whitening teeth by one shade in 3 days. You may be pleased to know, our research does confirm reduction of tobacco stains, when used in accordance with the usage directions (as mentioned on the packaging of the toothpaste). Hope this helps you make an informed choice of using Colgate Visible White O2 toothpaste.see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdbff124495ad843fc8"},"product_asin":"B09PNV9C37","QAs":[{"question":"Manufacturing date ?","answer":"Hi Sourav Shekhar, glad to know of your interest. Colgate Active Salt Toothpaste is best to use before 24 months from the manufacturing date. While we won‚Äôt be able to share specific information for the product that would be shipped to you, this information is printed on the packaging as well as on the rear/crimp end of the toothpaste tube in \"MM/YY\" format ( MM represents the month and YY the year of manufacture). Hope we have answered your question. Thanks!\"see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbddff124495ad843fca"},"product_asin":"B00I6F64T2","QAs":[{"question":"This paste pack of 2?","answer":"100g 2 pieces.","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket üõí","date":"2022-07-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it erode tooth enamel?","answer":"Enamel becomes all the more stronger. Gums also become stronger. Teeth are protected from decay.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbddff124495ad843fcd"},"product_asin":"B082LDRTD1","QAs":[{"question":"What's the expiry date of this pack?","answer":"Every pack has the date printed","votes":"0","username":"VENKAT","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"I wonts to buy colgate 500 gm but there is buy option","answer":"Buy the available pack","votes":"0","username":"JKSingh","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many Colgate pack in 800gm jumbo pack?","answer":"4 tubes of 200 gm each","votes":"0","username":"BTC MART","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"This item is original Colgate toothpaste","answer":"Not sure, it's very dry.","votes":"0","username":"Pranab D.","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many tube in boxes","answer":"Hi Tusar, thank you for reaching out. This is a 700 gm special offer with 4 packs of Colgate Strong Teeth Toothpaste. This pack contains 3 tubes of 200gm and 1 tube of 100gm. Hope this helps. Many thanks!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which toothpaste is the best for our teeth","answer":"I prefer Colgate strong teeth, but obviously the original one.","votes":"0","username":"Pranab D.","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does a toothpaste ‚Äúboost‚Äù Calcium??","answer":"Hi Peter Griffin, Colgate Strong Teeth Anticavity Toothpaste is formulated with Calcium which helps in restoring teeth‚Äôs natural calcium levels that get depleted every time we eat. The product does deliver the benefits mentioned when used in accordance with the usage directions, as mentioned on the packaging. We do hope the information is helpful. Thanks for writing in!see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Flouride is not mentioned?","answer":"Hi Peter Griffin, you can be sure all ingredients used in the product are well tested, researched and absolutely safe for use. Also, these ingredients are listed on our products packaging for easy reference. Should you have any further questions, please feel free to reach out through email /call us (information available on the product packaging) for us to connect with you. Thank you so much!see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date when the date of expiry","answer":"Hi Vanlalhruaii, glad to know of your interest. Colgate Dental Cream Toothpaste is best to use before 24 months from the manufacturing date. While we won‚Äôt be able to share specific information for the product that would be shipped to you, this information is printed on the packaging as well as on the rear/crimp end of the toothpaste tube in \"MM/YY\" format ( MM represents the month and YY the year of manufacture). Hope we have answered your question. Thanks!\"see less","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many grams and prices in pack","answer":"Hi Akanksha, as shown on the description product photographs you will be receiving 4 * 175 gram toothpaste tubes for Rs. 243 /-. We hope this clarifies. Thanks for writing in.","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good to clean car headlight whennit becomes dull ??","answer":"Hi, Colgate Dental Cream Toothpaste provides anti cavity protection with regular use. The product does deliver the benefits mentioned when used in accordance with the usage directions, as mentioned on the packaging. Thanks for checking!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdeff124495ad843fd8"},"product_asin":"B0B2PVXWZS","QAs":[{"question":"How much Past should use on brush?","answer":"Pea Size only","votes":"0","username":"aswedlock","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the taste of the toothpaste?","answer":"No taste","votes":"0","username":"aswedlock","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdfff124495ad843fdd"},"product_asin":"B07JFW4CY4","QAs":[{"question":"This one is colgate salt","answer":"Hi, this is not Colgate Salt, as shown on the description product photographs it is a pack of 4 tubes of 150g of Colgate Max Fresh Peppermint Toothpaste. Hope this clarifies. Many thanks!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it expired prod as the Expiry date mentioned by seller is 01july 2021..plzz confirm to me that exactly what is its expiry date ????","answer":"No it's not. The seller sometimes don't update the expiry date for years but they always provide the fresh toothpastes.","votes":"0","username":"Ajay Chambial","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdfff124495ad843fe0"},"product_asin":"B07QL37M78","QAs":[{"question":"Can i know the manufacturering date of the product?","answer":"On the tube","votes":"0","username":"us pathania","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbdfff124495ad843fe2"},"product_asin":"B0755J7HRX","QAs":[{"question":"What is today's MRP and expiry?","answer":"Don‚Äôt know exact price but definitely less than market price and expiry near to this year","votes":"0","username":"Shaikh‚Ä¶","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Blue or red, which is better?","answer":"I have not tried the blue one. But red is good.","votes":"0","username":"JITESH LAHIRI","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it flouride free?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH JETHANAND BHOJWANI","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mera order diya hai payment bi diya uska kay hua","answer":"You will get the delivery at your doorstep as indicated by Amazon via email and SMS .","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH JETHANAND BHOJWANI","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6303cbe6ff124495ad84402a"},"product_asin":"B07G4CMNPQ","QAs":[{"question":"what is the expiry date?","answer":"Check expiry date before order","votes":"0","username":"MOHAMMAD MOHSIN KHAN","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
